class FlashCard {
  final String front;
  final String back;
  final String spokenWordSound;
  final String neutralSound;

  FlashCard({
    required this.front,
    required this.back,
    required this.spokenWordSound,
    required this.neutralSound,
  });
}

final List<FlashCard> flashcards = [
  FlashCard(front: 'Forder', back: 'Woman', spokenWordSound: 'forder_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound1_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Fellot', back: 'Eye', spokenWordSound: 'fellot_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound2_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Gamper', back: 'Place', spokenWordSound: 'gamper_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound3_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Poters', back: 'Money', spokenWordSound: 'poters_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound4_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Setaks', back: 'Kind', spokenWordSound: 'setaks_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound5_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Biacom', back: 'Day', spokenWordSound: 'biacom_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound6_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Junint', back: 'System', spokenWordSound: 'junint_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound7_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Relled', back: 'Story', spokenWordSound: 'relled_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound8_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Tiazes', back: 'Business', spokenWordSound: 'tiazes_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound9_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Infamo', back: 'Problem', spokenWordSound: 'infamo_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound10_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Sayour', back: 'Lot', spokenWordSound: 'sayour_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound11_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Behers', back: 'People', spokenWordSound: 'behers_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound12_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Zorban', back: 'City', spokenWordSound: 'zorban_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound13_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Cander', back: 'Man', spokenWordSound: 'cander_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound14_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Remink', back: 'Month', spokenWordSound: 'remink_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound15_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Exotor', back: 'Part', spokenWordSound: 'exotor_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound16_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Shodle', back: 'Book', spokenWordSound: 'shodle_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound17_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Bliels', back: 'Gloves', spokenWordSound: 'bliels_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound18_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Skiled', back: 'Dog', spokenWordSound: 'skiled_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound19_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Chirds', back: 'Government', spokenWordSound: 'chirds_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound20_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Plurce', back: 'Area', spokenWordSound: 'plurce_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound21_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Ething', back: 'Hand', spokenWordSound: 'ething_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound22_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Berset', back: 'Way', spokenWordSound: 'berset_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound23_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Caludo', back: 'Time', spokenWordSound: 'caludo_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound24_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Morode', back: 'Home', spokenWordSound: 'morode_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound25_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Sponed', back: 'Job', spokenWordSound: 'sponed_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound26_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Conded', back: 'Life', spokenWordSound: 'conded_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound27_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Stamed', back: 'Family', spokenWordSound: 'stamed_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound28_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Farric', back: 'Child', spokenWordSound: 'farric_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound29_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Seigns', back: 'Car', spokenWordSound: 'seigns_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound30_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Insing', back: 'Fact', spokenWordSound: 'insing_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound31_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Onwars', back: 'Water', spokenWordSound: 'onwars_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound32_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Medged', back: 'Group', spokenWordSound: 'medged_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound33_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Groven', back: 'Work', spokenWordSound: 'groven_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound34_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Leards', back: 'Number', spokenWordSound: 'leards_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound35_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Uphers', back: 'Study', spokenWordSound: 'uphers_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound36_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Weaser', back: 'House', spokenWordSound: 'weaser_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound37_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Trapts', back: 'Issue', spokenWordSound: 'trapts_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound38_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Jashew', back: 'Friend', spokenWordSound: 'jashew_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound39_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Humboy', back: 'Company', spokenWordSound: 'humboy_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound40_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Holvia', back: 'Point', spokenWordSound: 'holvia_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound41_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Jumbon', back: 'Right', spokenWordSound: 'jumbon_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound42_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Honchy', back: 'Week', spokenWordSound: 'honchy_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound43_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Milets', back: 'Tree', spokenWordSound: 'milets_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound44_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Batmus', back: 'Year', spokenWordSound: 'batmus_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound45_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Unding', back: 'Side', spokenWordSound: 'unding_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound46_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Wooker', back: 'Service', spokenWordSound: 'wooker_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound47_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Loasto', back: 'Backpack', spokenWordSound: 'loasto_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound48_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Carmed', back: 'Blanket', spokenWordSound: 'carmed_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound49_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Oraved', back: 'Belt', spokenWordSound: 'oraved_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound50_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Hingly', back: 'Stairs', spokenWordSound: 'hingly_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound51_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Decils', back: 'Bench', spokenWordSound: 'decils_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound52_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Clobia', back: 'Door', spokenWordSound: 'clobia_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound53_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Gulloy', back: 'Brush', spokenWordSound: 'gulloy_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound54_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Delons', back: 'Socks', spokenWordSound: 'delons_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound55_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Wirade', back: 'Helmet', spokenWordSound: 'wirade_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound56_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Lested', back: 'Badge', spokenWordSound: 'lested_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound57_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Exiloy', back: 'Sculpture', spokenWordSound: 'exiloy_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound58_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Wiloyd', back: 'Firewood', spokenWordSound: 'wiloyd_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound59_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Carged', back: 'Vase', spokenWordSound: 'carged_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound60_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Veeble', back: 'Toaster', spokenWordSound: 'veeble_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound61_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Plekel', back: 'Camera', spokenWordSound: 'plekel_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound62_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Vecren', back: 'Pants', spokenWordSound: 'vecren_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound63_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Rullar', back: 'Necklace', spokenWordSound: 'rullar_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound64_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Stonge', back: 'Pillow', spokenWordSound: 'stonge_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound65_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Fillog', back: 'Shoes', spokenWordSound: 'fillog_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound66_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Helega', back: 'Cat', spokenWordSound: 'helega_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound67_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Bumore', back: 'Bracelet', spokenWordSound: 'bumore_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound68_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Infary', back: 'Painting', spokenWordSound: 'infary_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound69_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Panner', back: 'Alarm', spokenWordSound: 'panner_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound70_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Breper', back: 'Knife', spokenWordSound: 'breper_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound71_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Genact', back: 'Umbrella', spokenWordSound: 'genact_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound72_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Burain', back: 'Candle', spokenWordSound: 'burain_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound73_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Delend', back: 'Jacket', spokenWordSound: 'delend_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound74_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Combly', back: 'Beads', spokenWordSound: 'combly_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound75_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Debuki', back: 'Earrings', spokenWordSound: 'debuki_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound76_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Shable', back: 'Guitar', spokenWordSound: 'shable_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound77_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Subuse', back: 'Spoon', spokenWordSound: 'subuse_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound78_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Pumoil', back: 'Dress', spokenWordSound: 'pumoil_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound79_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Poldly', back: 'Freezer', spokenWordSound: 'poldly_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound80_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Jemylo', back: 'Bag', spokenWordSound: 'jemylo_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound81_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Retand', back: 'Plant', spokenWordSound: 'retand_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound82_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Rarbon', back: 'Purse', spokenWordSound: 'rarbon_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound83_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Glamed', back: 'Scissors', spokenWordSound: 'glamed_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound84_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Pixine', back: 'Glass', spokenWordSound: 'pixine_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound85_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Moster', back: 'Tray', spokenWordSound: 'moster_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound86_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Broove', back: 'Flask', spokenWordSound: 'broove_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound87_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Praled', back: 'Radio', spokenWordSound: 'praled_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound88_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Bushor', back: 'Lamp', spokenWordSound: 'bushor_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound89_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Combal', back: 'Microwave', spokenWordSound: 'combal_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound90_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Forres', back: 'Shirt', spokenWordSound: 'forres_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound91_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Pupens', back: 'Wallet', spokenWordSound: 'pupens_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound92_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Naxori', back: 'Dish', spokenWordSound: 'naxori_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound93_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Kroggy', back: 'Sunglasses', spokenWordSound: 'kroggy_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound94_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Riving', back: 'Hammer', spokenWordSound: 'riving_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound95_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Brexon', back: 'Computer', spokenWordSound: 'brexon_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound96_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Jazing', back: 'Clock', spokenWordSound: 'jazing_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound97_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Cented', back: 'Bicycle', spokenWordSound: 'cented_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound98_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Wafect', back: 'Stool', spokenWordSound: 'wafect_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound99_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Lunned', back: 'Armchair', spokenWordSound: 'lunned_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound100_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Pelone', back: 'Comb', spokenWordSound: 'pelone_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound101_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Litire', back: 'Screwdriver', spokenWordSound: 'litire_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound102_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Punser', back: 'Headphones', spokenWordSound: 'punser_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound103_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Auters', back: 'Watch', spokenWordSound: 'auters_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound104_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Motier', back: 'Oven', spokenWordSound: 'motier_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound105_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Miffer', back: 'Window', spokenWordSound: 'miffer_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound106_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Chimer', back: 'Ring', spokenWordSound: 'chimer_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound107_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Uphols', back: 'Broom', spokenWordSound: 'uphols_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound108_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Batton', back: 'Table', spokenWordSound: 'batton_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound109_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Plange', back: 'Hat', spokenWordSound: 'plange_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound110_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Grunds', back: 'Phone', spokenWordSound: 'grunds_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound111_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Sheels', back: 'Jeans', spokenWordSound: 'sheels_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound112_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Gunder', back: 'Pen', spokenWordSound: 'gunder_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound113_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Comery', back: 'Scarf', spokenWordSound: 'comery_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound114_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Taloda', back: 'Skirt', spokenWordSound: 'taloda_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound115_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Postic', back: 'Television', spokenWordSound: 'postic_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound116_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Incons', back: 'Tie', spokenWordSound: 'incons_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound117_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Coyage', back: 'Plate', spokenWordSound: 'coyage_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound118_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Pryind', back: 'Sofa', spokenWordSound: 'pryind_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound119_normalized.wav'),
  FlashCard(front: 'Nepeng', back: 'Fork', spokenWordSound: 'nepeng_normalized.mp3', neutralSound: 'CueSound120_normalized.wav'),
];